坐下来苦想是没有用的 宝贝
It ain't no use to sit and wonder why, babe
你至今还是没能弄清
Even you don't know by now
坐下来苦想是没有用的 宝贝
An' it ain't no use to sit and wonder why, babe
怎么着也不会有用了
It don't matter anyhow
天色破晓 公鸡开始啼鸣
When your rooster crows at the break of dawn
你朝窗外看去
Look out your window
而我已经走远
I'll be gone
让我重回旅途的缘故在于你
You're the reason I'm trav'lin' on
不过不必多想了 这没什么
Don't think twice, it's all right
打开你的那盏灯是没有用的 宝贝
It ain't no use in turnin' on your light, babe
我从未见识过的那盏灯
That light I never knowed
打开你的那盏灯是没有用的 宝贝
An' it ain't no use in turnin' on your light, babe
此刻我身处路途的暗面
I'm on the dark side of the road
可是我依然渴望你能有所行动
but I wish there was somethin' you would do or say
来让我回心转意 留下别走
To try and make me change my mind and stay
我们过去交流实在太少了
We never did too much talkin' anyway
不过不必多想了 这没什么
So don't think twice, it's all right
呼唤我的名字也是没有用的 亲爱的
It ain't no use in callin' out my name, gal
从前你可没这样做过
Like you never did before
呼唤我的名字也是没有用的 亲爱的
It ain't no use in callin' out my name, gal
我已经什么也听不见了
I can't hear you any more
一路上我在思考着一个问题
I'm a-thinkin' and a-wond'rin' walkin’ down the road
我曾经爱上一个男人 我说他是个孩子
I once loved a man, a child I'm told
我交出了我的心 他却想要我的灵魂
I gave him my heart but he wanted my soul
所以不必多想了 这没什么
So don't think twice, it's all right
再见了 亲爱的
So long, Honey Babe
去往何方 我不能讲
Where I'm bound, I can't tell
但是“拜拜”这词太过甜美
But goodbye's too good a word, gal
我还是说“别了”为好
So I'll just say fare thee well
我不想说你过去对我不好
I ain't sayin' you treated me unkind
你可以做得更好的 但也没事儿了
You could have done better but I don't mind
你有点在浪费我宝贵的时间
You just kinda wasted my precious time
不必多想了 这没什么
But don't think twice, it's all right
Don't think twice, it's all right
不必多想了 这没什么